"use strict";
let answerDATA = [
	{'id':1,"total":3,"rows":[{"id":4,"level_id":1,"type":0,"question":"In which year did Chinese President Xi Jinping propose building a Silk Road Economic Belt?","answer":"B","option":[{"num":"A","value":"A. 2012 "},{"num":"B","value":"B. 2013 "},{"num":"C","value":"C. 2014 "},{"num":"D","value":"D. 2015"}]},{"id":2,"level_id":1,"type":1,"question":"The Belt and Road Initiative was first proposed by Chinese President Xi Jinping at Nazarbayev University in Kazakhstan.","answer":"A","option":[{"num":"A","value":"True"},{"num":"B","value":"False"}]},{"id":1,"level_id":1,"type":0,"question":"When did the Belt and Road Initiative come forward?","answer":"B","option":[{"num":"A","value":"A. 2012.3"},{"num":"B","value":"B.2013.9  "},{"num":"C","value":"C.2014.9 "},{"num":"D","value":"D. 2015.6"}]}]},
	{'id':2,"total":3,"rows":[{"id":6,"level_id":2,"type":0,"question":"How many Belt and Road cooperation documents have these countries and international organizations signed with China?","answer":"B","option":[{"num":"A","value":"A.188  "},{"num":"B","value":"B.198 "},{"num":"C","value":"C.167"},{"num":"D","value":"D.142"}]},{"id":5,"level_id":2,"type":0,"question":"How many countries and international organizations have signed Belt and Road cooperation documents with China?","answer":"C","option":[{"num":"A","value":"A.112 "},{"num":"B","value":"B.134 "},{"num":"C","value":"C.167"},{"num":"D","value":"D.182"}]},{"id":3,"level_id":2,"type":0,"question":"Which of the following is included in the six major economic corridors of the Belt and Road?","answer":"A","option":[{"num":"A","value":"A.China-Mongolia-Russia Economic Corridor (CMREC)"},{"num":"B","value":"B.New Eurasian Land Bridge (NELB)"},{"num":"C","value":"C.China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC)"},{"num":"D","value":"D.All of the above"}]}]},
	{'id':3,"total":2,"rows":[{"id":8,"level_id":3,"type":1,"question":"The United Nations has set up a special mechanism called the United Nations Maritime & Continental Silk Road Cities Alliance (UNMCSR) for international affairs concerning the Belt and Road.","answer":"A","option":[{"num":"A","value":"True"},{"num":"B","value":"False"}]},{"id":7,"level_id":3,"type":0,"question":"In which dynasty of China did the ancient Silk Road originate?","answer":"A","option":[{"num":"A","value":"A. Han Dynasty "},{"num":"B","value":"B. Yuan Dynasty "},{"num":"C","value":"C. Tang Dynasty "},{"num":"D","value":"D. Ming Dynasty"}]}]},
	{'id':4,"total":4,"rows":[{"id":12,"level_id":4,"type":1,"question":"On February 19, 2016, Chinese President Xi Jinping reviewed the Xinhua Silk Road project during his visit to the Xinhua News Agency and he spoke highly of it.","answer":"A","option":[{"num":"A","value":"True"},{"num":"B","value":"False"}]},{"id":11,"level_id":4,"type":1,"question":"The BRInfo platform designed for sharing information and conducting cooperation among member institutions of the BREIP is constructed by Xinhua Silk Road, a national Belt and Road economic information service platform, which is under China Economic Information Service(CEIS), Xinhua News Agency.","answer":"A","option":[{"num":"A","value":"True"},{"num":"B","value":"False"}]},{"id":10,"level_id":4,"type":0,"question":"Whatâ€™s the founding date of the Belt and Road Economic Information Partnership (BREIP)?","answer":"B","option":[{"num":"A","value":"A. June 27, 2018 "},{"num":"B","value":"B. June 27, 2019 "},{"num":"C","value":"C. November 3, 2019"},{"num":"D","value":"D.June 26, 2019 "}]},{"id":9,"level_id":4,"type":1,"question":"The Belt and Road Economic Information Partnership (BREIP) initiated by Xinhua News Agency has been included in the List of Deliverables of the Second Belt and Road Forum for International Cooperation.","answer":"A","option":[{"num":"A","value":"True"},{"num":"B","value":"False"}]}]}
]